http://www.geminipickups.co.uk/privacy

Login
Wish List (0)
Shopping Cart
Checkout
Categories
Humbucker
Vintage (6)
Classic (4)
Contemporary (6)
Magick Series (5)
Special Series (11)
7 & 8 String (6)
HB Sized Mini (7)
HB Sized Singles (5)
Other
Rickenbacker (9)
Jazzmaster (7)
HB Sized Singles (5)
Show All Other
Bass
Jazz Bass (3)
Precision Bass (4)
Rickenbacker Bass (3)
Thunderbird Bass (3)
Other Bass (7)
Show All Bass
T-Shirts
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyThe Gemini Pickups website requires some cookies in order to function correctly. If you block cookies, you may not be able to use the website successfully and may not be able to order from us.  You can still purchase Gemini Pickups , by ordering through email and receiving a PayPal invoice.We only acquire and store personal information as far as is necessary for legal compliance (e.g. with tax laws) and for essential purposes regarding transactions. We do not collect or store any payment or other sensitive information.We do not provide any personal information to third parties for marketing purposes.We do not provide any personal information to third parties at all except as required for the functioning of the website shop and associated payments and/or for reasons of legal compliance.We retain personal information only for purposes of warranty management.If you choose to create an account with us, the information you enter will be stored in our databases. You may choose to delete your account and the information associated with it at any time.Your privacy is your right and we respect it in full
By using this website you give permission to use cookies for your best shopping expirence More Information
Understood
